<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Adventure Time!</title>
    <link>http://example.com/categories/season6/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on Adventure Time!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://example.com/categories/season6/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Sad Face (Season 6)</title>
      <link>http://example.com/posts/season-6-sad-face/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/posts/season-6-sad-face/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The episode begins with &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Neptr&#34;&gt;Neptr&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/BMO&#34;&gt;BMO&lt;/a&gt; spying on a sleeping Finn and Jake. Neptr asks BMO what is going to happen and asks the cause of their spying to which BMO tells him to just watch, as this happens once in a month and also promises it would happen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The scene changes to Jake and suddenly, his tail starts to wiggle. BMO points out this is what he called Neptr for, and they observe as Jake&amp;rsquo;s tail starts to move. Neptr is fascinated by it, and they follow Jake&amp;rsquo;s tail and spy on it. They sneak with the tail in the living room, and find that the tail has got a hat on his head. It further moves to get a cloth and packs some berries in it, and goes out of the treehouse. Neptr asks that where does the tail go, to which BMO replies it is none of their business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The tail passes under a horse and through a bush to reach a tiny circus. The &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Ringmaster&#34;&gt;Ringmaster&lt;/a&gt; notices him, and refers to him as Blue Nose, hinting the tail must have worked for quite a time. He tells Blue Nose that he is late, and tells him to put on his makeup. Blue Nose obeys him and goes to a makeup room. The scene changes to inside the circus, where a blind grasshopper is throwing knives at a target at which another ant is tied on. The crowd is fascinated as a knife pierces the target just near the ant. Blue Nose is shown in the makeup room applying a white substance at the lower end, and painting a &amp;lsquo;blue nose&amp;rsquo;, and a sad face.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The scene again is changed at the circus and this time, the waving &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Snail&#34;&gt;Snail&lt;/a&gt; is performing a jump in a water pot, in which it succeeded and the crowd cheers. The snail exits, and a poor quality music starts playing. Blue Nose enters the arena with a cart of oranges and shows an act of taking an orange and rolling it in ground. The crowd observes it without any expression. Blue Nose finds a puppet bee in the cart, and wakes it up. It wakes up, and Blue Nose puts him on the ground. They both dance for a moment, then suddenly the bee dies and is taken off stage. Due to this boring act, the crowd criticizes Blue Nose, however, there is one little ant which is seen touched by the act and crying, although nobody notices her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The crowd throws various things at Blue Nose for an unimpressive act and Blue Nose exits from the arena. The Ringmaster is also bored by it and further criticizes Blue Nose. The Ringmaster then enters and announces an upcoming of a fierce performance and says it is about a dangerous beast in captivity. He announces the appearance of a chipmunk named Goralina, who is led by six ants and is in chains. They take Goralina on a raised platform and make it sit there. Blue Nose starts to see this, and sees the Ringmaster cruelly beating the chipmunk to perform for him. An audience throws an empty bottle of bug milk on its eye, to which she becomes enraged and breaks out of the chains and starts attacking the Ringmaster. She takes almost all of the crowd in its mouth. Blue Nose comes with a movable staircase and reaches near Goralina. He starts to hypnotize the chipmunk and succeeds. The grasshopper from an earlier act comes and throws the knife at Goralina. The chipmunk gets hypnotized and throws out the crowd she engulfed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The scene then fades out to the place of the Ringmaster. He is seen trying to put a 5 cent coin in a small box. Blue Nose approaches and the Ringmaster welcomes him. He talks about the show going completely wrong. He says that Goralina had given him a good amount of money the last show and is disappointed that no one rivaled Goralina today. He says there is another show in an hour and says to come up with an interesting act that will rival to the performance of her. Blue Nose is saddened by the fact that the chipmunk is kept there without her will, and goes to the cage of Goralina. He sees a sign indicating not to feed the monster. He rips it off and offers the berries he bought which she eats. Then he thinks about his next show and goes to his equipment chest. He sees a whoopee cushion and takes it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The scene fades to the arena and shows Blue Nose entering. He starts his same song used in the last show, and the Ringmaster thinks he will still perform the same bad act. Blue Nose instead goes to the middle, where there is a chair with a cushion on it. As soon as he sat on the cushion, it made a farting sound, to which the crowd laughed. The Ringmaster is awestruck and sees as the act continues. Blue Nose takes the whoopee cushion and throws it, and then proceeds to sit, but the chair breaks and the crowd laughs. He then goes to fill his water tumbler, but the water container throws water at his face. He starts to wrestle with it, but it kept throwing out water and the crowd laughed at it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He then proceeds to change his music to more hip type, but the record player doesn&amp;rsquo;t do this and he breaks it and the crowd laughs yet again. After his act, the crowd starts throwing money at him and Blue Nose approaches the Ringmaster. He is quite pleased with Blue Nose and says if he and Goralina perform, they would make this show a success. Blue Nose gets angered by him, and proceeds to use a whip on him. Thinking that it was part of an act, the audience cheers, laughs, and applauds. Goralina is arrived in chains but Blue Nose helps her to break out and they start running.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They are escaped from the circus, but due to the fact that Blue Nose is Jake&amp;rsquo;s tail and was just stretching, its trails were still in the circus, and so the Ringmaster pulls him back. He starts to slap him and one of the ants who was slapping him smeared his hat on his mouth, which changes expression from sad to that of happy. They ask him why is he happy, but he just waits and as soon as the first ray of sunlight strikes him, he begins to undo all his stretching, and finally reaches Jake, who wakes with a snap. Finn notices Jake and says nothing as he does not know it, but the episode ends with Neptr and BMO giggling.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Tower (Season 6)</title>
      <link>http://example.com/posts/season-6-the-tower/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/posts/season-6-the-tower/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The episode starts with Finn trying to make spaghetti with a bulky candy arm. His bulky arm doesn&amp;rsquo;t help Finn and he starts destroying things and as he continues to mess things up, he gets frustrated and his candy arm explodes. &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Jake&#34;&gt;Jake&lt;/a&gt;comes down stairs, hoping for the spaghetti, but instead sees the mess and tells him that he should just take his time and listen to his &amp;ldquo;Melon Heart.&amp;rdquo; Finn then says he wants to go to space so he can take &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Martin&#34;&gt;his father&lt;/a&gt;&amp;rsquo;s arm. Jake tells him not to do this but to just relax and think and that he&amp;rsquo;s going to the store to buy replacement kitchen supplies for the ones Finn broke. Finn goes outside the tree fort and he lies on the ground. He starts to talk to himself and then suddenly he notices a pile of rocks forming behind him and that there is an odd, sightly transparent arm, where his real arm used to be. He then decides to use this arm to build a tower into space to find his dad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As Jake is returning home, the tower has grown considerably and &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Princess_Bubblegum&#34;&gt;Princess Bubblegum&lt;/a&gt; is there and tells Jake that Finn&amp;rsquo;s got a new arm, what she believes to be a telekinetic electro-emotional prosthesis and is dangerous and could hurt him and other people around him. Jake shakes off the notion and says what Finn&amp;rsquo;s doing is healthy and he should just be left alone. As Finn continues his tower he enters the cloud house of a &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Cloud_People&#34;&gt;Cloud person&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Carroll&#34;&gt;She&lt;/a&gt; tells Finn to leave, and when he doesn&amp;rsquo;t, blasts him with lightning with her gun. This moves the house out of the tower and the cloud person then says that Finn must be, &amp;ldquo;One of those swimmers,&amp;rdquo; and leaves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next day large chunks of Ooo&amp;rsquo;s landscape are missing because of the tower, including a rookery of &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Penguins&#34;&gt;penguins&lt;/a&gt;. The cloud person from the day prior returns to Finn, introduces herself as Carroll and apologizes and asks if he&amp;rsquo;s really going to take his father&amp;rsquo;s arm. Finn states that he is and the cloud person talks about how she was water once and how swimmers would always be swimming in her, so she got evaporated and became air. She then tells Finn he should let it go, runaway, and hate his life like she has.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the ground &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/BMO&#34;&gt;BMO&lt;/a&gt; asks Jake what Finn is doing (not before getting crushed into the ground by a falling ice block). Jake says Finn&amp;rsquo;s just working some stuff out and that it&amp;rsquo;s completely healthy, which is directed at PB who is working on some sort of device. PB disagrees and says that Finn could get hurt. As Finn&amp;rsquo;s tower has finally reached the atmosphere, Carroll asks what it&amp;rsquo;s like up there and wonders if she should become space ice. Finn, who is extremely oxygen deprived, sees a similar looking portal to the one the &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Void_Caster&#34;&gt;Void Caster&lt;/a&gt; made in &amp;ldquo;&lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Escape_from_the_Citadel&#34;&gt;Escape from the Citadel&lt;/a&gt;,&amp;rdquo; but suddenly a bright light comes at him and he blacks out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finn then wakes up in what seems to be a space ship and walks to the next room to see his &amp;lsquo;father&amp;rsquo; watching TV. Finn surprises his father and punches him into unconsciousness and tries to take his arm. As Martin moans about his favorite arm, Finn changes his mind and it is revealed that Martin was really a disguised PB. She says she tricked Finn and took him to the &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Candy_Kingdom&#34;&gt;Candy Kingdom&lt;/a&gt; fallout bunker, and since he had so little oxygen that he was already hallucinating, the trick was easy to pull off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finn returns home, with his telekinetic arm gone, and tells Jake that he&amp;rsquo;s calmed down. Jake says that&amp;rsquo;s great and asks if Finn wants to do the honors of taking down the tower. Finn says he would and removes a plank of wood near the base of the tower, which then collapses sideways, destroying a large portion of the Candy Kingdom, to the shock of Finn and Jake. The episode ends with Princess Bubblegum screaming, &amp;ldquo;AHHH! MY ARM!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>James II (Season 6)</title>
      <link>http://example.com/posts/season-6-james-ii/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/posts/season-6-james-ii/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The episode begins with Finn, Jake, and Bubblegum walking and looking for a flower called a Weeping Willy. Once they find it, they start collecting its tears, when Clone James fakes his death claiming that the ground below Bubblegum is loose and performs a fake attempt to save her. He falls into the river and yells, &amp;ldquo;Remember me!&amp;rdquo;. A flashback is shown of the occurrences of the episode &amp;rdquo;&lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/James&#34;&gt;James&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;rdquo; Finn and Jake feel sorry for him, pointing out that it was the 25th time James had sacrificed himself for Bubblegum. Princess Bubblegum then tells them that James faked his death, and points out that the ground near the flower is perfectly solid, and there is no possibility of her falling into the river.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;test&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finn and Jake then tell her to bring him back by cloning him, but she tells them that the fake deaths are getting out of hand and it is pointless to award him for his foolish behavior. She says that it&amp;rsquo;s time for him to go into an eternal nap. Finn and Jake protest against her and persuade her to bring him back, but she stands on her ground and declares that there would be no more Jameses. She then tells Finn and Jake to clean up James&amp;rsquo;s apartment to which they reluctantly agree.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As they make their way to his apartment, they start talking about his &amp;lsquo;sacrifices&amp;rsquo;, like eating a contaminated cupcake for PB. When they reach the apartment, open the door and switch on the lights they are surprised to find lots of Jameses and ask them who&amp;rsquo;s in charge. A clone James comes forward wearing a lot of medals and introduces himself as James #2. They ask him to explain the scene, to which he replies he was lonely, and wanted more companionship. He knew PB wouldn&amp;rsquo;t make another James, unless he died a hero, so he started faking his death to collect medals, saying that medals make him happy. Jake tells Finn that Princess would be upset about this, to which James #2 gets scared and tells them not to convey this to her. He also tries to bribe them by giving them a medal, but the duo refuse. They say that they won&amp;rsquo;t warn the Princess, because she will eventually find out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finn and Jake go outside and then sit on a bench, laughing at the scene. After some time, they see the Princess whistling and going to James&amp;rsquo; apartment. As soon as Princess enters the building, she shouts, &amp;ldquo;Hey!&amp;rdquo; and all of the Jameses start running out of the house to random places. Finn and Jake enjoy it and laugh. The scene then changes and shows the original James and other Goo Monsters heading out of the pit and towards the kingdom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The scene then returns to the Candy Kingdom, showing Finn and Jake sitting on the walls of the kingdom, and looking below. They see the Princess assembling the Banana Guards and showing them a picture of James. The Banana Guards understand, but as soon as Princess says there are 25 of them, the Banana Guards get all confused and ask questions, such as &amp;ldquo;How can one picture identify all 25?&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Are they brothers?&amp;rdquo; Princess Bubblegum angrily answers their questions. Finn and Jake laugh at their stupidity, when PB notices them and asks for their help. They invite her to their place, and she goes along, while muttering. She arrives at their place, and asks why they are sitting down doing nothing. Jake tells her to sit for 5 minutes and enjoy it. She sits down, and Jake offers her some wall candy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They look below as a Clone James comes to their place. The Banana Guards don&amp;rsquo;t identify him, and even ask him if he has seen the James in the picture. Even Clone James couldn&amp;rsquo;t identify himself which causes the three watching from above to laugh. Eventually, all the Jameses try and cannot identify their own picture. The Banana Guard in charge takes the photo back and asks the name of the first Clone James. He then asks all their names and all of them claim to be &amp;lsquo;James&amp;rsquo;, and say that their names are the same, &amp;ldquo;because they look alike.&amp;rdquo; The Banana Guard then comes to a random conclusion that they are brothers, to which the Jameses reply otherwise. The Banana Guard counts them but the Clone Jameses reassures that there are 25 of them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Banana Guard then puts his mental power to work and recalls the orders of PB. He then tells his other guards that they are the guys Princess was talking about.They finally try to capture them while Finn, Jake, and PB laugh at this. The scene then changes to the Banana Guards randomly trying to capture all the Jameses, and in the end, they manage to capture them all. While all this is happening, the Original James and the horde of Goo Monsters arrive at Candy Kingdom, unnoticed. Princess Bubblegum arrives at the place where all Jameses are captured, and snatches their medals, saying they are not heroes. Suddenly, a Gumball Guardian shouts, &amp;ldquo;Evil presence detected!&amp;rdquo; and points to the horde of Goo Monsters. The Banana Guards are then ordered to protect the Candy Kingdom. They obey the order, but since they don&amp;rsquo;t usually fight, some fake their death and one even jabs a spear into his body to fake it. Finn intervenes and uses the spear to attack the Monsters, but on contact with their bodies, the spear melts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finn then warns everyone not to touch them, as anything that touches them melts. The Banana Guards get scared and run into the kingdom. Finn notices some Candy Orphans playing there. He asks Jake for help to bring them inside the kingdom. As they get busy with this task, the Jameses notice PB in danger. They notice the Original James attacking her, and then try to save her by dogpiling on him and fusing together. This causes the Original James to be fused with the clones and be killed. The Jameses say, &amp;ldquo;We told you we were heroes!&amp;rdquo;. Afterwards, Princess Bubblegum awards the medals back to the Jameses. She then gives them a new assignment, which is to &amp;ldquo;go to the wasteland and never come back.&amp;rdquo; The Jameses protest, but Princess Bubblegum interrupts them and tells them she would send them a medal every day. They agree to this and run to the wasteland. The episode ends with Princess Bubblegum saying, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m not gonna miss him.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>